<resources>
    <string name="app_name">淡商校務通</string>

    <string name="appAdMob">*****************************</string>
    <string name="AdMob">**********************************</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="not_login">尚未登入</string>
    <string name="click_to_login">點擊登入</string>
    <!--menu  -->
    <string name="campus_information">行事曆</string>
    <string name="school_timetable">靠北淡商</string>
    <string name="semester_results">學期成績</string>
    <string name="lack_of_records">學期記錄</string>
    <string name="OnlineRepair">線上報修</string>
    <string name="Traffic">交通資訊</string>
    <string name="about_us">關於我們</string>
    <string name="sing_out">登出</string>
    <string name="close">關閉</string>
    <string name="no_NetWork">目前沒有網路連接</string>


    <string name="about_author_title">作者</string>
    <string name="about_author_content">方毅恆</string>
    <string name="about_thx_title">特別感謝</string>
    <string name="about_thx_content">鄭賓少</string>
    <string name="about_contact_us">聯絡我們</string>
    <string name="about_open_source_title">MIT License</string>
    <string name="github_link">https://github.com/vn7n24fzkq/TSVS_Application</string>
    <string name="about_open_source_content">MIT License

Copyright (c) 2017 VN7

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="json_license">simplejson</string>
    <string name="json_license_content">"Apache License
Version 2.0, January 2004
http://www.apache.org/licenses/
TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION
1. Definitions.
"License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,
and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.

"Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by
the copyright owner that is granting the License.

"Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all
other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common
control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,
"control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the
direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or
otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the
outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.

"You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity
exercising permissions granted by this License.

"Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,
including but not limited to software source code, documentation
source, and configuration files.

"Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical
transformation or translation of a Source form, including but
not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,
and conversions to other media types.

"Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or
Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a
copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work
(an example is provided in the Appendix below).

"Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object
form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the
editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications
represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes
of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain
separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,
the Work and Derivative Works thereof.

"Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including
the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions
to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally
submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner
or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of
the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted"
means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent
to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to
communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,
and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the
Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but
excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise
designated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."

"Contributor" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity
on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and
subsequently incorporated within the Work.

2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,
publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the
Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.

3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of
this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,
worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable
(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,
use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,
where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable
by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their
Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)
with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You
institute patent litigation against any entity (including a
cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work
or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct
or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses
granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate
as of the date such litigation is filed.

4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the
Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without
modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You
meet the following conditions:

(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or
Derivative Works a copy of this License; and

(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices
stating that You changed the files; and

(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works
that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and
attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,
excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of
the Derivative Works; and

(d) If the Work includes a "NOTICE" text file as part of its
distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must
include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained
within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not
pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one
of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed
as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or
documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,
within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and
wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents
of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and
do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution
notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside
or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided
that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed
as modifying the License.

You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and
may provide additional or different license terms and conditions
for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or
for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,
reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with
the conditions stated in this License.

5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing
the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,
and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,
or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this
License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only
on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf
of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,
defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability
incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason
of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.

END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS

APPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.

To apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following
boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "[]"
replaced with your own identifying information. (Don't include
the brackets!)  The text should be enclosed in the appropriate
comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a
file or class name and description of purpose be included on the
same "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier
identification within third-party archives.

Copyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner]

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License."
</string>
    <string name="weather_license">中央氣象局 OPEN DATA</string>
    <string name="weather_license_link">http://data.gov.tw/?q=principle</string>
    <string name="weather_license_content">政府資料開放授權條款－第1版
中華民國104年7月27日訂定
為便利民眾共享及應用政府資料、促進及活化政府資料應用、結合民間創意提升政府資料品質及價值、優化政府服務品質，訂定本條款。

一、定義

(一)資料提供機關：指將職權範圍內取得或作成之各類電子資料，透過本條款釋出予公眾之政府機關（構）、公營事業機構、公立學校及行政法人。

(二)使用者：指依本條款規定取得開放資料，並對其利用之自然人、法人或團體，包括依本條款授權使用者再轉授權利用之人或團體。

(三)開放資料：指資料提供機關擁有完整著作財產權，或經授權得再轉授權第三人利用之資料，並以公開、可修改，且無不必要技術限制之格式提供者，包括但不限於下列著作：

1. 編輯著作：選擇、編排具有創作性，而可受著作權法保護之資料庫或其他結構化資料組合。

2. 素材：指開放資料集合物中，其他可受著作權法保護之獨立著作。

(四)衍生物：指依本條款所提供之開放資料，進行後續重製、改作、編輯或為其他方式利用之修改物。

(五)資訊：指不受著作權法保護之純粹紀錄，並隨同開放資料一併提供者。前揭資訊除本條款授與權利之規定外，比照有關開放資料之規定辦理。

二、授與權利

(一)各機關所提供之開放資料，授權使用者不限目的、時間及地域、非專屬、不可撤回、免授權金進行利用，利用之方式包括重製、散布、公開傳輸、公開播送、公開口述、公開上映、公開演出、編輯、改作，包括但不限於開發各種產品或服務型態之衍生物。

(二)使用者得再轉授權他人為前項之利用。

(三)使用者依本條款規定利用開放資料，無須另行取得各資料提供機關之書面或其他方式授權。

(四)本條款之授權範圍不包括專利權及商標權。

三、課予義務

(一)使用者利用依本條款提供之開放資料，視為同意遵守本條款之各項規定，並應以尊重第三人著作人格權之方式利用之。

(二)使用者利用依本條款提供之開放資料，及後續之衍生物，應以符合附件所示「顯名聲明」要求之方式，明確標示原資料提供機關之相關聲明；未盡顯名標示義務者，視為自始未取得開放資料之授權。

四、版本更新及授權轉換

(一)本條款如有修正，依舊條款提供之開放資料，於新條款公告時，使用者得選擇採用新條款利用。但原資料提供機關，於提供開放資料時，已訂明其使用之特定版本條款者，不在此限。

(二)本條款與「創用CC授權 姓名標示 4.0 國際版本」相容，使用者依本條款利用開放資料，如後續以「創用CC授權 姓名標示 4.0 國際版本」規定之方式利用，視為符合本條款之規定。

五、停止提供

有下列情形之一者，各資料提供機關得停止全部或一部開放資料之提供，使用者不得向資料提供機關請求任何賠償或補償：

1. 因情事變更或其他正當事由，致各資料提供機關評估繼續提供該開放資料供公眾使用，已不符合公共利益之要求。

2. 所提供之開放資料，有侵害第三人智慧財產權、隱私權或其他法律上利益之虞。

六、免責聲明

(一)依本條款提供之開放資料，不構成任何資料提供機關申述、保證或暗示其推薦、同意、許可或核准之意思表示；各資料提供機關僅於知悉其所提供之開放資料有錯誤或遺漏時，負修正及補充之責。

(二)使用者利用依本條款提供之開放資料，受有損害或損失，或致第三人受有損害或損失，而遭求償者，除法令另有規定外，各資料提供機關不負任何賠償或補償之責。

(三)使用者利用依本條款提供之開放資料，因故意或過失，致資料提供機關遭受損害，或第三人因此向資料提供機關請求賠償損害，使用者應對各機關負賠償責任。

七、準據法

本條款之解釋、效力、履行及其他未盡事宜，以中華民國法律為準據法。

附件：顯名聲明

提供機關／單位 [年份] [開放資料釋出名稱與版本號]
此開放資料依政府資料開放授權條款 (Open Government Data License) 進行公眾釋出，使用者於遵守本條款各項規定之前提下，得利用之。
政府資料開放授權條款：http://data.gov.tw/?q=principle

</string>

    <string-array name="cowbei_array">
        <item>靠北淡商</item>
        <item>投稿靠北</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="results_array">
        <item>歷年成績</item>
        <item>月考成績</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="records_array">
        <item>缺曠紀錄</item>
        <item>獎懲紀錄</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="select_grade">
        <item>一年級</item>
        <item>二年級</item>
        <item>三年級</item>
        <item>四年級</item>
        <item>畢業</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_traffic">TrafficActivity</string>

    <!-- <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>-->
</resources>
